89 days ago I arrived here with real in my pocket
and I didn't even imagine living it all bro
I cleaned windows
chairs
I passed with dog
I delivered flyers
sell truffle
and all this still sleeping inside 1 Chevette
Real until tomorrow
during this whole time I tried to create 1 business
parental authorization
1st were several ideas of failures
I thought I'd open a coffee
a pet shop
create a marketing agency inside the shed
but i realized they were all going to limit me
in physical space
not Kombi here
I can travel around Brazil
and set up my mobile office
it was sleeping in chevas that i learned
that we don't need comfort to have courage
was cleaning windows and delivering flyers
that I also learned
that we don't need much to start
is on
I met Juninho
or
and I learned that family is not the blood that welcomes
there when i failed my first workshop
I learned that failure is not even the end
I desist that it is
I got bigger rain here
or is it closed
but that's it man
and it was because of this failure that i created 1 movement
called
beatbox
it's been 90 days looking for a business I loved
when in fact
it was all right in front of me
if I were sure from day one
I wouldn't have lived and given up
everything I've experienced in these three months
and I wouldn't be here inside that bus either
and wouldn't have the courage to say
no
Education